{
   "T-spots":{
      "type":"marker",
      "items":[
         {
            "coords":[
               51.963886,
               7.610546
            ],
            "name":"Botanical Garden",
            "popup":"Botanical Garden",
            "qset":[
               {
                  "Question":"When was the botanical garden built?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"1800"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"1813"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"1803"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"1795"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"C"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"In 1990's what feature was added to the garden?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Stream"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Pond"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Medicinal greenhouse"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Nothing"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"How many of the 280 known Pelargonium species are present in the garden?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"15"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"230"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"275"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"140"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"B"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"The Bromeliad house contains pineapple plants from which part of the world?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Nordic region"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Central Africa"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"South-east Asia"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"South and Central America"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What is the spaciality of the Farntal area?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Mountain plants"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Rock roses and olive"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Plants from grasslands"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Ferns"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               }
            ]
         },
         {
            "coords":[
               51.962900,
               7.629437
            ],
            "name":"St. Lamberti Church",
            "popup":"St. Lamberti Church",
            "qset":[
               {
                  "Question":"When was the Church built?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"1275"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"1375"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"1475"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"1575"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"B"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Who financed the building of Church?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Merchents of the city"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Duke of Paris"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Vatican"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Governer of Muensterland"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What hangs at the tower of the church?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"3 wooden buckets"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"3 cooper swords"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"3 iron baskets"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"3 cooper bells"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"C"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Who's representation lies on the west facade of the church?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Bernhard Knipperdolling"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Johann Wolfgang von Goethe"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Jan van Leiden"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Friedrich Schiller"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"B"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What landmark is to the east of church?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Domplatz"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Lambertikirchplatz"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Rye market"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Old fish market"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               }
            ]
         },
         {
            "coords":[
               51.948110,
               7.587544
            ],
            "name":"All-weather Zoo",
            "popup":"All-weather Zoo",
            "qset":[
               {
                  "Question":"When was the current All-weather zoo built?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"1972"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"1973"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"1974"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"1975"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"C"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Who is the current zoo director?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"H. JÃ¶rg Adler"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Helmut Reichling"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Hermann Landois"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Thomas Wilms"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What category of animals share the joint top count with Fish as of start of 2016?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Invertebrates"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Amphibia"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Birds"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Reptilies"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What is major attraction at the Robben Haven show?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"California Sea Lions"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Westphalian Horses"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Asian Elephants"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Penguin"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What are Lories?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Penguin"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Elephants"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Vultures"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Parrots"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               }
            ]
         },
         {
            "coords":[
               51.960801,
               7.624331
            ],
            "name":"LWL Cultural Museum",
            "popup":"LWL Cultural Museum",
            "qset":[
               {
                  "Question":"Which artist from Die Bruke movement does the museum specializes on?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Erich Heckel"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"August Macke"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Fritz Bleyl"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Emil Nolde"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"B"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Which kind of painting does the museum has an extensive collection of?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Byzantine"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"fresco"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Romanesque"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"spÃ¤tgotik"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"When is the museum entry free for students?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Every 1st day of month"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Every last weekend of month"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Every second friday of month"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"All days"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"C"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Which section is present in west wing of first floor of the museum?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Modern contemporary art"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Roman christian paintings"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Paintings focused of Peace"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"None of the above"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What is the count of inventory in the museum library?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"100,000"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"130,000"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"90,000"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"190,000"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"B"
               }
            ]
         },
         {
            "coords":[
               51.956902,
               7.618507
            ],
            "name":"Aasee-Giant Pool Balls",
            "popup":"Aasee-Giant Pool Balls",
            "qset":[
               {
                  "Question":"When was the waterbus 'Professor Landois' built?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"1972"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"1973"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"1974"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"1975"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"C"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What was Petra who visited Aasee in 2006?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Black Swan"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Black Crane"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Black Kite"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Crow"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"What did the artist Wilm Weppelmann installed at Aasee?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Floating baloons"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Floating status of Elephant"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Floating vegetable garden"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Floating replica of Dom"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"When did the lake got its current day structure?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"1944"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"1930"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"1919"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"1934"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"D"
               },
               {
                  "Question":"Name of the vehicle bridge on Aasee?",
                  "Options":[
                     {
                        "A":"Tormin"
                     },
                     {
                        "B":"Tomin"
                     },
                     {
                        "C":"Tronim"
                     },
                     {
                        "D":"Tromim"
                     }
                  ],
                  "Answer":"A"
               }
            ]
         }
      ]
   },
   "T-Zones":{
      "type":"zone",
      "items":[
         {
            "center":[
               51.963886,
               7.610546
            ],
            "radius":200,
            "name":"Botanical Garden zone"
         },
         {
            "center":[
               51.962900,
               7.629437
            ],
            "radius":200,
            "name":"St. Lamberti Church"
         },
         {
            "center":[
               51.948110,
               7.587544
            ],
            "radius":200,
            "name":"All-weather Zoo"
         },
         {
            "center":[
               51.960801,
               7.624331
            ],
            "radius":200,
            "name":"LWL Cultural Museum"
         },
         {
            "center":[
               51.956902,
               7.618507
            ],
            "radius":200,
            "name":"Aasee-Giant Pool Balls"
         }
      ]
   }
}